Thần chết à??
Thưa bố, mẹ, chuyến đi của bố mẹ như thế nào?
Con vẫn thế, rất phiền toái
cái lời nguyền có thể lấy đi sinh mạng của những gì con chạm vào này.
Không có dâu hiệu rằng sẽ biến mất.
Thưa cô chủ, lại một con vật khác được cậu Bocchan chạm vào và...
Sống chung nhà với thằng bé này khiên ta chết lặng.
Hãy gửi nó đếnh dinh thự.
Cứ như là đứa con của thần chết
Tại sao phù thủy lại đặt lời nguyền này lên con?
Có một sứ làm con phiền lòng ạ.
và đó là....
bocchan, trà của ngài đã chuẩn bị xong rồi ạ.
Gần quá đấy!
"Tập 1: Công tước and và Alice"
Aren't you going to send that letter?
I couldn't!
I haven't written a letter in so long.
It was for practice.
This is really good!
Thank you.
My maid's name is Alice. I have no
idea what goes on in her head.
She knows if I touch her,
she'll die, but...
It's rather chilly today, isn't it?
She says one thing and does the opposite.
Every day she tries to get a rise out
of me, and then watches how I react.
What's wrong, Your Grace?
What are you doing?
I thought you wanted me to...
I didn't drop my head
down to see up your skirt!
I keep telling you to lay off
the sexual harassment!
It makes it hard for me!
I'm sorry.
But I can't stop!
You're awfully sure about that!
You should put your own safety first.
You're the one maid who'll stay with me.
I don't want to lose you.
I don't know what I mean to you, but...
How about another cookie?
Were you listening to me?
Up to the part where you said,
"I don't know what I mean to you, but..."
Then you heard all of it!
And you just ignored me!
There's still one left.
Please clean your plate.
Fine, I will.
Don't make weird noises!
That was an indirect kiss, wasn't it?
You didn't have to say
that out loud, did you?
I take the life of anything I touch...
A witch put this curse
on me when I was five.
Who she was, where she
came from, or why she did it...
...my memory fails me.
"No one shall love you,
and you shall love no one."
"You shall live a life of misery."
All I remember are the witch's words.
Turning her back on me, my mother
gave me this mansion in the forest,
and I haven't seen my family since.
If only I could break the curse,
I could go home.
To the home where I belong...
What are you doing, Your Grace?
Alice! N-Not this again!
I told you to lay off
the sexual harassment!
You always react so innocently. It makes
me want to tease you all the more!
Alice is the only daughter of the head
maid at my family's residence.
I've known her since she was a child.
I hadn't seen her for a while,
until about two years ago,
when for reasons I don't
understand, she came here...
Your Grace.
Cheer up.
That won't make me feel better!
You stopped, then started again!
Alice, cut it out!
I may not look like it,
but I'm a man, you know!
What if I give into temptation
and touch you?
Do you want to touch me?
Stop toying with me...
Good morning, Your Grace.
Why do you have to get so close?
What if you touched me accidentally?
This is awful...
She saw the weird faces
I make in my sleep.
I brought you your breakfast.
I'm not hungry. And there's way too much.
That's what you said when
you skipped dinner last night.
Your mother used to insist that you eat
three square meals a day, didn't she?
It's not fair of you to
bring up my mother.
I'm worried about you.
What if you should fall ill...
...and never be able to spend your
nights fooling around with me again...
Spend my nights doing what with you?!
It's true, I do feel bad that I never
finish the food you make me.
I can eat a little, I guess.
Okay, say aah.
You really want to feed me, huh?
She's staring at the inside of my mouth!
I'm sorry, I don't get many
chances to see inside your mouth.
--I couldn't help it.
--Well, don't!
As an apology, would you care
to have a look inside my mouth?
Y-You don't have to show it to me!
I'll eat on my own.
Hand me the fork.
Here you are.
Your Grace, why are you
so uninterested in eating?
Why?
Because ever since I was cursed,
mealtimes were the worst part of the day.
It's been slow, but ever since you
came here, I've started to eat more.
I'm grateful, even if I don't look it.
I'll clear away these dishes.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Your Grace, your childhood friend
Philip says he'd like to see you,
as it's been too long.
Mother, it seems that Philip
was here just now.
That's none of your concern, dear.
I told him I'd see him, but now that
the day is here, I'm getting cold feet.
Is it too late to refuse?
Send him a letter saying
I can't meet today.
It's too late for that. Just accept it.
Do you remember Philip?
Indeed. He was a lively young boy,
very unusual for a noble's son.
He used to chase you around
with a snake in his hand...
...or throw bugs at you.
Yeah, he was a bit of a troublemaker.
But...
...you're looking forward
to meeting him, aren't you?
H-H-Hello there!
Don't peek inside my room!
Anyway, it's been so long
since we've had guests.
I'll change into my formal attire.
Very well. I'll take your
tuxedo out of storage.
Now, about that hat...
I'm absolutely,
positively not taking it off!
My naturally curly hair and these circles
under my eyes make me look so uncool.
I need to hide them with a hat, at least.
I don't think so at all.
You have hair that people love to curl
around their fingers, mysterious eyes,
and such kissable lips...
I'll get your tuxedo ready.
Will this do?
Thank you, Alice.
You can leave while I change.
No, I'll help.
I can change on my own!
I can't take my clothes off
in front of a girl!
Would you feel less self-conscious
if we both took our clothes off?
What on earth are you thinking?!
If you don't start taking your
clothes off, I'll take mine off first.
What kind of threat is that?!
To be honest, I'm a little
hopeful about today.
I gathered as much.
Make sure you don't touch me directly.
Of course.
When I was cursed, and my family
and friends all started to avoid me,
he was the one person
who looked at me differently.
I've never forgotten that.
Now that the day is here, I feel
nervous about meeting him, but...
...if he's willing to give
me another chance,
perhaps we can be friends again.
I'll put your tie on, then.
Oh, thank you.
Stay still.
You're too close!
Don't yell into my ear, please.
Don't behave like this
when Philip is around.
I just don't want another man
to see your bare skin.
Don't worry. I only do it for you.
I-I see.
Then, I guess that's okay...
It's only fun if I get
to see your reaction.
Scratch that! It's not okay!
H-Hello there, Philip.
Y-Yeah. Thanks for having me.
How many years has it been?
You're not going to throw
bugs at me, are you?
Bugs? What are you talking about?
Have you forgotten? You used to
play all kinds of pranks on me.
You've really mellowed out.
That's so long ago
I don't remember it, but...
I'm sorry!
N-No, it's not that I wanted
you to apologize...
My Lord!
Don't worry.
They're just... um... making a cool pose!
The fact that I'd gotten my hopes
up only makes it feel worse.
So, what do you want, Philip?
No, um... It's nothing special.
I just wanted to see an old friend...
Say, aren't you the daughter
of the family's head maid?
Yes. You remembered me?
Yes, I remember you well.
Why are you working here as a maid?
Is it just the two of you living here?
Normally I have a butler as well.
He hurt his back and is resting.
But he'll be back soon.
I-I see.
Your Grace!
I'm fine.
What about you?
W-We're fine!
Are you leaving so soon?
Yeah. We've talked enough.
I'm sorry, where is the lavatory?
I'll show you the way.
Yes?
Just hear me out.
Why don't you come back to town with us?
It's dangerous for you to stay with him.
I'll find you another job, if you like.
You must leave this place at once.
No.
Why not?
Has he threatened you? Or...
Philip!
Don't say anything that
would cause her trouble!
You can disrespect me all
you want, but not Alice!
Your Grace, please calm down.
S-Stay away!
Don't come near me, you monster!
I-I didn't even want to come here...
Then why did you?
Your mother wanted me
to see how you were doing.
There's talk of having your younger
brother inherit the family title.
Knowing your family, if that happens,
they'll cut off ties with you entirely.
My Lord?
I'm okay. I'll be right there.
I may be scared of you,
but I pity you, too.
Telling you the truth is
my way of making amends.
I'm sorry about all this.
I'll never come back here again.
Farewell.
Your Grace...
I'm totally fine!
Let's just forget about it
and have dinner.
Let me know when it's ready.
You're so good at the piano...
Let's play again sometime!
We'll always be buddies!
This curse will be broken...
Or it won't...
My family will accept me again...
Or they won't...
Alice loves me...
She loves me not...
Your Grace?
Dinner is ready.
Are you feeling better now?
Oh, uh-huh...
I'm a lost cause...
Whenever you're away, I always think about
things that make me feel ill at ease.
My past self. My future self.
And my present self.
I've got no confidence in anything.
I bet you hate me, too.
I feel like I don't even
have the right to love you.
I can't touch you...
I'll never know the heat of another's
body nor the warmth of their tears.
If I wanted to give you a present...
...even a flower, it will just
wilt in my hands.
Philip was right. I'll never go back
to the house I grew up in.
I'll remain a monster that everyone
has turned their back on--
Your Grace.
Didn't you know?
In the language of flowers,
a wilted white rose means
"to swear your whole life to someone."
This is more than enough
of a present for me.
Let's break your curse together.
Someday...
...I'd like to put a ring on your
finger with my own hands.
I see... So that's how it is.
Yes. There's no sign of
the curse being broken,
but he seems to be
leading a peaceful life.
Thank you.
You may leave.
Thanks for such a wonderful meal.
You ate quite a lot.
Yeah... I guess it's because
I was feeling kind of tense today.
Alice,
thanks for always making
such delicious meals.
I'll go on making them.
Breakfast, lunch, and dinner.
Just for you, Your Grace. Always.
"The Duke of Death and His Maid"
The Duke, His Butler, and a Lost Cat.