Can you imagine...
...a life in which you could never
touch the one you love?
He takes the life of whatever he touches.
That was the curse the witch put on him.
Plants, animals... and people
are no exception, of course.
Regarding her son, doomed to live his life
without knowing the warmth of another,
his mother only complained.
"That child is like Death incarnate..."
she said.
You're getting too close to me
again today, Alice! Way too close!
Your reactions are so adorable,
Your Grace,
I can't help wanting to see them up close.
Okay then, take this!
I won't get self-conscious
if I can't see you!
You truly are adorable, Your Grace.
My ears are totally defenseless!
"Episode 2: The Duke, His Butler,
and a Lost Cat"
Please forgive me for my extended absence.
I have fully recovered
from my back injury,
so I shall be returning
to work as of today.
That's wonderful.
Good to have you back, Rob.
I imagine I caused you
some trouble as well, Alice.
I left the care of His Grace
entirely in your hands.
You needn't worry about me.
I was able to spend the night
together with His Grace, so...
Stop saying things that
could be misconstrued!
Seeing you two always
puts a smile on my face.
You need to keep your subordinate
from sexually harassing me!
And now, I shall take my leave.
It's the morning after Rob got back,
and it looks like he's already
hard at work around the estate.
Yes, even doing the jobs that
are too much for me to handle.
He's superhuman. That's why.
Rob's been a butler to me from the
time I lived at my family's residence.
He was also the only one
to come with me to this estate.
You could say he was like a father to me.
So, how long do you plan
on standing there?
Rob has taken all the work
I would normally do.
Does my presence here bother you?
Well, it's just that I can't
concentrate on my reading...
I hope I'm not disturbing you.
I've brought you your tea.
But he was just in the yard a moment ago!
Aren't you working a bit too hard, Rob?
Who, me?
Well, you are sort of on the mend and all.
Why don't you let Alice
do some of the work, too?
How kind of you to worry.
I may have been a bit too eager to get
back to work after my absence, but...
...you needn't worry about me, Your Grace.
Very well. We'll divide the cleaning to be
done around the estate and get to work.
Let's go, Alice.
All right.
What is with her?
This is really good!
Rob's work hasn't
suffered any, to be sure.
It may be boorish of me to worry.
Still...
Alice?
There's something I wanted to ask you...
I-It's me! What the heck
are you doing, Rob?
Oh, it's you, Your Grace.
Forgive me. My eyes have been blurry
lately, and it makes things hard to see.
That's a sign of aging eyes!
I've told you before, haven't I?
That lately, the effects of your
old age have gotten a bit worse.
If you touch me, you'll die.
That doesn't mean I want
you to avoid me, but...
...you have to look out
for yourself a bit more.
And you're hard of hearing, too!
What's the matter?
Oh, Alice, it's you.
Can you talk some sense into him?
Pardon me.
This is the real Alice, right?
It's Alice! She's the only
other person around here!
I don't get it.
Your work is flawless, and yet...
When you've been a butler for as long as
I have, your body remembers the work.
So, you needn't worry about me.
I shall serve you for as long
as I live, Your Grace.
Rob...
Is it your back again?
So it seems...
All right. This is sounding good.
In case my family decides to disown
me somewhere down the road,
I've been writing a bunch of songs
so I can make a living with my music.
For as long as I can remember,
the only thing I ever got praised for...
...was my piano playing.
Having still not found any way
of breaking the witch's curse,
playing the piano is my dream
as well as my only hope.
Is that a requiem?
Forgive me. While I was cleaning, I heard
this beautiful song being played, and...
In that case, could you come up and
speak to me more like a normal person?
What do you mean by "normal"?
I mean, "Don't lean in so close to me"!
Don't bug me, okay?
Rob is resting, so just do your own work.
Very well.
It's not like...
...I'm giving into...
...my baser emotions or anything...
Your Grace,
you're staring too hard.
I bet you were doing it on purpose!
Since I can't concentrate,
save the cleaning for later and...
...come sit here and listen
to me play until I'm done.
All right.
Looks like I've got a front-row seat.
I wouldn't go so far as to say that.
It's a somber yet very beautiful song.
You know what?
You told me it sounded
like a requiem earlier,
but I actually composed it
as a ballad for you.
I almost didn't ask you because
I was too embarrassed to,
but after thinking about it some more,
I really wanted you to hear it with me.
I'm feeling a bit tired,
so I think I'll take a nap.
Wake me up when dinner's ready.
I see. Very well...
...I shall kiss you good night.
I was only kidding. If you're going
to take a nap, please do it in bed.
Well, that sure woke me up!
May I please be excused?
You barely touched your plate.
I'm on a diet. Please give me
a smaller helping tomorrow.
Hey, I'm starving. Don't we have
any apple crumble or something?
Didn't you say you were on a diet?
Come on, who cares?
Oh, that's right! I'm going out tomorrow,
so get the carriage ready.
It's so peaceful...
I'm making really good progress.
Looks like I'll get
more done than I planned.
Oh, this mansion's as depressing as ever!
For being so run-down,
it's ridiculously huge!
The stress of just being here
would make me break out in zits!
Definitely bad for the skin!
I don't know how he manages to live here!
Oh, there you are!
I'm so sorry.
You're so unobtrusive I didn't
even notice you were there!
How long has it been, Dearest Brother?
Alice! Alice, come quick!
What's the matter?
You let her in the house again
without my permission, didn't you?
What a rude thing to say!
Lady Viola is Your Grace's
younger sister, so...
That's right.
I have so graciously come to visit you,
so why don't you act happier?
It seems my dearest brother
wishes to speak with me,
so wait for me in the garden.
Yes, milady.
Nobody asked for this!
Mmm! This is great!
Tea is best served with
sweet crumpets, don't you think?
I don't think I could ever get my fill.
When are you planning on leaving today?
Oh, my God! How rude!
You don't have to tell me to go.
I'm not staying long.
Mother will be angry with me
if she finds out I'm here.
Hey, can I have some more sweets?
And some Assam tea brewed
with dried fruits, too!
Very well.
You've really got a lot of nerve!
My sister loves girly things like sweets
and talking about her love interests.
I suspect she drops by occasionally
for a little change of pace.
But...
Hey, what are you looking at?
So, not only are you gloomy and unpopular,
you're also into very young girls?
...I just can't handle her
"charming" personality.
I brought you some sticky toffee pudding.
Wow! It looks delectable!
Sorry to put you to all this trouble.
It was no trouble at all.
Say, are you fond of that maid,
Dearest Brother?
Huh?!
Um... I'm fond of her...
I mean, I adore her...
That was painful to watch.
Hey, that hurts!
Well, that explains it.
My dearest brother's in love.
Oh, well.
Little Miss Viola here will just have to
make you popular, starting with that maid.
Using "The Viola Method of
Instruction in the Art of Love."
The Viola Method?!
For example, everybody's got a
complex about something, right?
All you've got to do is
just hide whatever it is.
I have a round face,
so I hide the contours.
And it melts everyone's heart.
See? Look how adorable I am!
Sounds like you're tooting
your own horn a bit too much.
In your case, Dearest Brother, you should
hide those dark circles under your eyes.
Y-You think?
--Like this?
--Eww! Pull it down some more.
Is this far enough?
I feared as much. You just don't have
what it takes to be a ladies' man.
Try again in the next life!
You sure do give up easily!
After all this chit-chatting with
Dearest Brother, it's gotten so late.
Well, I was able to eat some tasty treats,
so I guess it wasn't a total waste
of time. I'll come again sometime.
Just stop dropping by unannounced, okay?
Or better yet...
Hurry up and break that curse so
you can come back and live with us.
What are you blushing for?
If you think I said that out of concern
for you, then you are sorely mistaken.
Who do you think you are, anyway?
You sure talk a lot of trash
on your way out...
Hey, what's the big idea--
Rob?!
Well, if it isn't Lady Viola!
Oh, um... H-H-How long has it been?
It's been ages.
I see you made a special trip all
the way out here just to pay us a visit.
I, um... wanted to see you, so...
Oh, you better be careful,
or your hair will get in your eyes.
Seems the Viola Method
is totally ineffective...
Who'd have thought she
was into very old men...
"Hurry up and break that curse," huh?
That's easy for her to say...
Alice! Alice, come quick!
What's the matter, Your Grace?
Why, it's a cat!
It must've wandered
in here from the forest.
I can't go into the piano room
as long as it's here.
Hurry up and shoo it out of here!
You truly are adorable, Your Grace,
to make such a fuss over a single cat.
I-It's not like I'm scared
of it or anything!
It's just that it's hard to
tell what animals will do,
so I get worried I might
accidentally touch them.
Here, kitty!
Did you hear me?
Yes, I heard you.
But I just love animals.
They're so adorable.
It has a collar.
Could it be a house cat?
Yeah, you're right. I wonder
if it ran away from home.
Let's set it loose in
the forest right away.
Wait a...
Why is it after me?!
Try not to fall, now!
What?! Come save me!
Huh? Your Grace...
You mustn't crawl around
on your hands and knees!
You think that looks like me?!
What you've got is worse
than a case of aging eyes!
I picked you up without thinking, but--
Hey! This feels like a cat!
Oh, how cute!
Don't get all friendly with it!
Run free, kitty cat!
And after you went to
the trouble of catching it!
Your Grace, the cat tore up
my clothes with its claws...
Is that something you've
got to tell me right now?!
But I can sew this up, and it'll be fine.
You don't have to widen
the rips with your fingers!
So, it was reacting to my bolo tie.
What a pesky cat!
It certainly is a drawback not
knowing what animals will do.
That includes you, too.
Stop fiddling with those rips!
What's this?
Your Grace, there's a note.
Could this be the cat's name?
Beats me.
Please forgive me...
What does this mean?
So, you didn't run away.
You were abandoned. Just like me.
It's hard... being cast aside.
Well, it looks like the cat
already found a new family.
Your tea is ready.
Please come in soon, Your Grace.
You wouldn't want to catch a cold.
All right, I'm coming.
In the gloom of the forest
I stand where I was abandoned
No one will hear
My feeble, heart-rending cry
I want to go back
But I can never go back
To that warm and loving place
that I miss so much
So, this is where you've been, Your Grace.
Your dinner is ready.
What have you been doing?
The moon is so beautiful, so I was
just standing here thinking.
I don't come in here much, but the view
from this ballroom certainly is lovely.
No one comes in here much
because there's no reason to.
Rob once told me that a long time ago,
my grandfather couldn't
dance to save his life,
so he used to come here
late at night to practice.
And apparently, his dance partner
at the time was your mother.
Don't you find that interesting?
My grandfather and your mother
danced in this very room.
I feel like it was fate
that brought us here.
It certainly could be an act of fate.
S-Shall we give it a try ourselves?
I can't touch you, but we can coordinate
our movements to approximate dancing.
I must decline.
Oh, I see... I thought it
would be fun, but...
Unless you ask me properly,
I must decline.
May I... have this dance?
I'd be delighted.
Aren't you a little too close?
Be careful not to touch me.
I'm used to it. It's just...
I haven't danced much at all.
Neither have I.
It's more difficult than I imagined.
But... it's delightful.
Alice, can I ask you something?
Certainly.
What do you think of me?
You're an important person.
No, not in the sense of
a master and his servant...
I'm asking you what you
think of me as a man.
Well, of course I like you, Your Grace.
Really?!
Why, yes.
I like you. I love you. I adore you. I
only have eyes for you, Your Grace.
All right, that's enough!
There aren't enough words
to express the way I feel.
I never would've thought you'd say that.
I think I'll have my dinner now.
Very well, Your Grace.
"The Duke and the Meteor
Shower During the Full Moon."