I have a girlfriend.
But then another girl confessed
her feelings to me.
What do I do?
I started going out with a girl recently.
I confessed my feelings to Saki-chan,
who I've been close to since we were kids.
She accepted, and now we're going steady.
Bam!
I'm the happiest person on Earth.
Sakisaki!
Come on, let's go.
Okay.
I'm headed off to my club.
I'll wait until you're done, Saki-chan.
You can go on ahead for once.
But no cheating on me.
S-Saki-chan!
Did you think I would do such a thing?
Naoya?
I'm sorry for making you worry!
I'll love you even more so you'll never
have to worry about me cheating on you!
Huh? Wait...
H-H-Hey!
Let me go!
I love you, Saki-chan!
Saki-chan!
Feel my love!
I feel it!
You feel it?
I get it! Jeez!
Save that for when we're alone!
Sheesh, Naoya...
You're beyond sincere. You're just weird.
You can't even take a joke.
A-Am I that weird?
You're pretty damn weird!
How?
Like what you did to me just now!
I... I see.
I never knew.
But I want to be true to my feelings.
I can't help but tell someone
I love them when I do.
Wh-What a pain.
I mean...
I confessed to you once a month
since we were in first grade.
Now, in high school, you finally said yes.
Of course I'm going to cherish you!
That was way too much for
elementary and middle school me!
But now you embrace my feelings for you!
Oh, damn it!
Bring it on!
Anyway, I'm going now.
Saki-chan!
What?
You were as cute as ever today!
Grrr
Thank you very much!
Ah...
I'm so happy that I have her.
U-Um...
You're M-Mukai Naoya-kun, right?
Yes, why?
Um, I...
I...
I have feelings for you!
Girlfriend, Girlfriend
Episode 1
"Even If That Isn't the Right Way"
Sorry, I haven't even introduced myself.
Wait... What?
Hello, I'm Minase Nagisa. I'm a first-year.
Nice to meet you.
Uh, yeah.
Um...
What do you think of me, looks-wise?
Huh? W-Well, if I had to be honest...
You're cute as hell.
Thank you!
I worked so hard these past
few months for this day.
Three months?
Four hours of working out,
jogging, and yoga every day.
Working on myself for three
hours before bed every night.
You're such a hard worker!
I wanted to be in my best
condition for my confession.
What an upright person you are!
They say the best way to a man's
heart is through his stomach, so...
I practiced cooking for eight hours, too.
Aren't you worried about your health?!
You have to take care of your own life!
I-I'm fine.
Really?
Y-Yes.
I'd like you to try it.
Delicious.
But you shouldn't put
yourself out for this.
No, it was for your sake.
In fact, I had fun doing it.
Besides, I think a big part of why it
tastes good is the Matsusaka beef,
Would you like a bag for this?
lobster, and foie gras that I bought
with money from my part-time job.
What a long day.
Raw Cost:
50,000 Yen
You overdid it!
B-But that's so commendable.
So, um...
Do I seem attractive to you?
Of course you do!
You're attractive as hell!
Th-Thank goodness.
Then...
Would you please go out with me?
Am I not good enough?
Th-That's not true!
I bet I'd be super happy
if I could go out with you.
But...
I already have a girlfriend.
I guess... I should have expected that.
But I'm not going to give up just
because I got turned down once.
I'll come confess to you again.
I-I'll talk to you later.
It's true that I have a girlfriend.
I love her, and I want
to treasure her forever.
Naoya-kun?
But it's true that I think you're attractive.
So I want you in my life.
I don't want to turn you down.
But I can't betray my girlfriend!
So if it isn't too outrageous to ask...
Can I date both of you?
Could you come with me to ask my girlfriend?
Eh?
I'm sorry this is the
only thing I can propose.
Uh... Um...
Let's go give it a try.
Thank you.
All right. Let's go.
Club
Meet
Girlfriend, Girlfriend
Go, Sakisaki!
Attack!
Man, I'm beat.
You killed it again, though.
Saki-chan!
Naoya?
Can I talk to you for a second?
You two sure are attached at the hip.
Wha... Shino!
I don't want to get in the way.
I'll see you later.
What's up? What's the big deal?
It's about this girl.
N-Nice to meet you.
I'm Minase Nagisa.
Sh-She's so cute!
Who is this girl? Oh my God, she's so cute!
Let's go hang out.
Okay? Can we?
But there's something important
we need to talk about.
How are we supposed to talk about anything
if we don't even know each other?
Good point.
Ta-da!
Karaoke!
Whoo!
S-Sorry. I'm not a good singer.
You're so cute when you're embarrassed.
Sports!
Go!
Right!
Your underwear's cute, too.
Hey!
This is too good!
I want to marry you!
I'm glad it's to your liking.
Saki-chan, what do you think of Minase-san?
Well...
Honestly, I want to go out with her!
I know that feeling.
Hold on a minute.
You have me, Naoya.
I do.
What's wrong?
So I want to date both of you.
Huh?
Huh? What?
Both of us?
The truth is, Minase-san just
confessed to me earlier today.
The more I got to know her,
the more attracted I became.
Honestly, I'm infatuated.
I can't...
I can't think of a solution besides
going out with both of you!
Wha?
What?
What?!
I don't quite understand.
I can't bring myself to date
both of you in secret.
So with your approval,
I would like to date both of you,
honest and out in the open!
Did you seriously think I'd say yes?
I-I want us to discuss this.
No way.
I really do feel bad about this.
Then don't do it!
You have me! Isn't that good enough?!
It was until yesterday.
I'll kill you.
Um...
Can we please avoid violence?
But you're okay with cheating?!
Actually, yeah!
How are you even okay with
him dating two girls?
W-Well...
I can't imagine Naoya-kun
would ever break up with you.
I'll only be rejected if I don't
have him date both of us.
So I'm okay with it.
No way!
Are you serious?
What do you even like so much about him?
Naoya-kun is everything to me right now.
That much?
Saki-san...
Please let us both date him.
T-Too cute!
Please don't look at me like that!
One guy for one girl!
Isn't that common sense?
But it's true that I'm
attracted to Minase-san.
So rejecting her and continuing
to go out with you
in the name of common
sense would be dishonest.
Both to myself and to you, Saki-chan.
Lying and going out with two girls
would both leave me with regrets.
So I want to be honest to myself
and try going out with both of you!
No.
What might I do to increase the
chances that you'll say yes?
No means no!
There must be a good solution to this!
Enough!
I won't spare any effort
to make it a success!
No, thank you!
Can we just try it?
Oh, for—
Please!
I'll make snacks every day!
You'll always have plenty to eat.
I'll take good care of you, Saki-chan.
I'll give you 30,000 yen every month.
What?!
I'll do anything in my power!
Why are you stripping?!
I agree that it's selfish of me
to want to date two girls.
I wholly expect you to dump
me right here and now.
Naoya...
And I'm sure Minase-san would prefer
if it were just me and her.
Still, Minase-san, Saki-chan...
I promise to make sure that, someday,
you'll be glad you both dated me!
Naoya-kun...
Oh, hell.
Why don't you try making me say that,
if you really think you can?
Saki-chan...
I don't think you'll ever do it.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
I already kind of hate you.
I-I'll do what I can!
I... I should have thought this through.
Girlfriend, Girlfriend
I...
I should have
thought this
through...
So what are we supposed to do now?
For you two to be all right with
both of you being my girlfriend,
you'll have to get to know each other better.
There's nothing good that can come of this.
I know!
Let's live together at my
place. The three of us.
What?!
I don't live with my parents. It'll be okay.
Hell no!
I-I'd be okay with that.
I'll bring my stuff.
Wai—
I'll let your mom know, Saki-chan.
Huh?!
W-Wait!
Um...
Are we seriously going to live together?
It's like a dream!
Okay, I'll prepare rooms for you two.
I'll prepare dinner, then.
And, um... Saki-chan...
I don't mean to brag, but I'm
terrible at doing chores.
Of course. You can take a break.
Yes, of course.
Really?!
Naoya, I want a snack.
Dinner's ready!
It smells so good.
Holy crap!
It's so good!
I'm so glad.
The bath's ready, too.
You're so thoughtful.
This is so nice.
Saki-chan, want me to rub your back?
You don't need to do that for me!
Well, I guess...
This might not be so bad.
Again?!
P-Pardon me.
Is it all right if we bathe together?
N-Nagisa-chan?!
T-Together?!
I'd like to talk with you.
May I?
I-I don't want to say no, but...
Thank you!
This is awkward.
Nagisa-chan's boobs are huge!
Her skin is so fair.
And so taut.
And her eyelashes are so long.
Saki-san...
Y-Yes?
Don't worry about me.
Please go ahead and sleep
with Naoya-kun tonight.
Huh?
S-Sleep?
Y-You're both young.
Feel free to do it.
No, no!
We aren't doing it!
Why not?
I must be getting in your way right now...
But I want to make sure
I don't do that too much.
No, um...
I'd feel bad if the two of you
had to go out of your way for me.
I mean, how do I put this...
We haven't done anything like that yet.
Y-You haven't?!
I'm sorry, I got ahead of myself.
I-It's fine.
But you can go ahead and
make out and stuff, too.
N-No, we haven't kissed
or anything yet, either.
I didn't realize.
You seem kind of happy!
No, I didn't mean it that way...
Are you sure?
I really hadn't realized, though.
You do seem happy!
Like, you're cute, but...
It hasn't even been that long
since we started going out.
And we've known each
other since we were kids,
and Naoya's weirdly stuck-up.
I see.
I-It's not anything to rush, right?
Let's work hard on those kinds
of things together, too, then.
O-Okay.
Naoya!
S-Saki-chan?!
How far do you intend to
take it with Nagisa-chan?!
H-How far?
In terms of sexy stuff!
Sexy stuff?!
W-Well?!
S-Sorry...
I do want to.
I knew it!
No, sorry, if I'm even more honest, well...
I'd like to do it with both of you...
the three of us, together!
Th-Th-The three of us?!
Naoya, you pervert!
I'm really sorry!
Don't get me wrong, though.
It's just a thought that came to my head.
It wouldn't be fair of me to hide it.
It's how you're so open about
it that makes you a pervert!
Nagisa-chan may be adorable,
and her boobs may be huge,
and she may have a nice body, and...
She gives me weird feelings,
even as a woman!
But that just makes it
even more unacceptable!
I understand.
This whole arrangement was
my imposition to begin with.
I can't ask you to do even
more for me, Saki-chan.
Naoya...
It's more important for the three of
us to establish a good relationship
than to do sexy things.
I'll give up on a three****.
Don't say that out loud!
So let's not do that kind
of thing together.
I understand.
O-Okay.
I'm glad.
Huh?
W-Wait...
Does that mean you aren't doing
anything with me, either?
Yeah...
I would be acting unfaithfully to
Minase-san if I was only with you.
I-I see...
Indefinitely?
Huh?
Y-You want to do sexy things?!
You definitely looked disappointed!
No! Th-That's...
I'm sorry!
You must be so curious about sex, Saki-chan.
N-No...
I'm sorry to make you abstain!
I mean, no... that's...
That's not the point!
Girlfriend, Girlfriend
Naoya's Message
to Saki's Mom
Saki-chan's Mother
May I have Saki-chan
over at my place for
a while?
Huh?
Sure, okay! Break a leg!
I'll do my best!
Don't worry,
I'll tell my husband
Preview
Episode 2
"How Nagisa Feels"
A Girlfriend's Two Choices!
If your boyfriend asks about dating
someone else at the same time, do you...
A: Break up.
B: Allow it.
C: Smack him!
You're already breaking the rules?!
And lop it off!
Lop what off?!
All right.
If you insist, Saki-chan.
Please don't undress!