Looking good.
Almost got him...
Opponent has lost connection.
Please remain on this screen until result is determined.
Damn it!
They always disconnect the
minute I start dominating.
I'll never move up the
leaderboard like this.
It might be time to stop playing this game.
Konpeito
Time for school, I guess.
A Day's Worth of Veggies
"Key"—perfect name for a latchkey kid.
Right?
I want to play a game.
A game to get immersed in, for however long.
A game to escape this reality of mine.
Say, isn't that Akira?
Wow. He's even gaming on the walk to school.
He's at it all day at school, too.
He never stops during classes or breaks.
But he's always top of the class
on the standardized tests, right?
Getting good grades is easy.
Formulas, grammar, vocabulary...
They're just testing how
much you can memorize.
Point is, he's a total weirdo!
Hush! He'll hear you!
I agree with her, honestly.
They say exams are a battlefield,
but they're barely even a competition for me.
I can't engage with them at all.
Receive a variety of objectives,
then beat the enemies
or clear the obstacles.
Games like that are the only
things I can really engage with.
That's why I find my current
reality so very bor—
What's your problem, asshole?!
He's only after me?
What's this guy's problem?
Should I call the police?
But I can't do that while I'm fleeing.
He'll catch me before I shake him off.
What do I do?
I need a counter-strategy.
A counter-strategy... almost like a game.
That's right.
The loss condition is, "He catches me."
And the win condition...
That's it.
If I treat it like a game,
I'll know just what to do!
That building would give
me the terrain advantage.
This building was abandoned
in the middle of demolition.
It's been left to the elements, crumbling.
For a big brute like him...
It'll take time to make his way up.
He just jumped it?!
What a freak.
I'd better treat this
scenario like survival horror.
I have to anticipate his next move.
Hey! Freak!
I did it!
He's still not down?!
He's coming?
With jumping power like his, he'll definitely—
attempt to jump his way up.
With sufficient planning and preparation,
any game can be beaten.
Congratulations to you, Akira Shiroyanagi!
Who'd have believed you'd beat
my little pet and survive?
Who is this woman?
How long has she—
But I'm sorry to say...
Even though you worked so hard...
This is what they call...
An unwinnable fight.
I couldn't... anticipate...
What's that?
If it's an unwinnable fight...
That means... it's not over?
Yes.
The fun's just getting started,
my sweet prince.
If the game's not over... then...
That's okay.
I'll win next time.
I want to play a game.
A game to escape this boring reality.
Episode 1   "Sophist"
Where am I?
Handcuffs?
Wait, she shot m—
I'm fine?
Ladies and gentlemen!
Hi there!
It's a pleasure to meet you all!
I'll be serving as your navigator!
The beautiful magician, Mion!
It's her!
Let me start with my congratulations.
You've been chosen to serve as our
project's esteemed focus group.
I will now explain how it works, with a
few marvelous illusions along the way!
First!
Everyone here has already been
removed from the national registry.
That's right! You're dead
in the eyes of society!
Dead?!
So it goes without saying that you
have no rights and no freedom,
except what you're allowed
by our rules and directives!
Second!
Hey!
Let's cut the bullshit already!
I do appreciate your kind assistance.
Behold!
That's my bullet-catching trick!
So she really can...
As you can see, I have the
"turn your hand into a cannon" ability!
And if fact, you've all been
gifted similar abilities!
In other words, you're our
ability testing focus group!
We've taken everything from you
and given you a unique ability in exchange!
Please use it to its fullest to run the
program we've arranged to completion!
But if we determine you useless
for providing product feedback,
we'll have to ask you to leave!
So do take this seriously!
Now I'll explain the program's rules.
First, those cuffs you're wearing...
They both restrict your movement and
prevent the use of your abilities.
When the red lights turn green,
it means they'll unlock in five seconds,
and you can use your abilities then.
You won't be penalized
for any harm or death
your abilities inflict on
other focus group members.
This concludes the program's rules.
Any questions? Anyone?
I'm under the impression
you enjoy games like this.
Any questions from you?
Class Representative Ringo Tatara?
Won't you be the first with your hand up,
the way you always are at school?
Madoka Kirisaki...
You're such a delinquent,
and this is a lot like a school lecture,
so I guess you might be struggling.
I know absolutely everything,
so don't be shy!
I have a question, then.
Shin Kumagiri?
Ask away!
Who are you people?
What is this place?
Why are you doing this?
I'm so happy you asked, but unfortunately...
None of those are questions I can answer!
Then I'll ask one more.
Why did you kill that man?
With power like yours,
you could have easily
stopped him non-fatally.
I know all about you, too,
so I know that you're a really good person.
But I killed that man because
I'm a really bad person.
Does that answer your question?
You—
It's thoroughly understandable.
We're all dead already anyway.
I'd bet you had that little magic
show planned from the start...
To make a point.
My, you're a clever one.
Okay! Any other questions?
Um... I have a question.
Yuuri Amagake!
Go right ahead!
No one else is asking,
so I guess I should...
Why did you choose us?
You seem to have learned all about us.
What were the criteria?
What a great question!
But you'll find the answer
pretty disappointing...
We chose you...
entirely at random.
That should take a weight
off your mind, right?
You basically won the lottery!
Think of it like a freak
traffic accident that—
Miss Mion!
I think it's about time.
Oh, Yang...
Is it time already?
The Q&A is over, then.
The first program will be one-on-one.
A series of simple duels.
I'll lead you all to your rooms now.
You can take that time to learn
and practice your abilities.
And one last reminder...
Consider how you should
approach this very carefully.
Absent
Akira Shiroyanagi
Present
This really is going like a game, I guess.
I'm curious about who these people
are, what they're after,
Konpeito
and various other things.
This room contains a bed, a toilet,
a refrigerator, objects your ability
applies to, ten sheets of paper,
and pencils. One-on-one battles end
through loss of consciousness, death, or
admittance of defeat. Your ability is written
on a separate sheet of paper (enclosed).
But the most important thing right now
This room contains a bed, a toilet,
a refrigerator, objects your ability
applies to, ten sheets of paper,
and pencils. One-on-one battles end
through loss of consciousness, death, or
admittance of defeat. Your ability is written
on a separate sheet of paper (enclosed).
is to find out my ability.
Receive your conditions and solve
the subsequent puzzles you face.
The game's difficulty will vastly change
based on the conditions presented.
Your
What in the world?
Oh, Akira...
That same boy again?
Oh, yes...
He's my personal favorite.
What in the world is this ability?
How am I supposed to use it?
Konpeito
Konpeito!
The sweetness! It stimulates the brain!
I guess they really do know me inside and out.
So much about this feels off...
That woman's actions, most of all.
Yes, it's almost like she...
Time Until One-on-One 18:41:37
Wh-What was that?!
Someone testing their ability?
That vibration and sound...
What if someone with a powerful
ability tries to kill me?
How could I use my ability to counter?
That's right...
No penalty for
harm or death
The things she said...
The rules laid out...
From the start...
She's been baiting us into killing each other.
An ability focus group? That's absurd.
But interesting.
Maybe I'll give it my best shot.
It's really coming together, Yang.
Such an excellent group.
They'll realize it soon, too...
How they should behave, when all
they have is their ability.
Now, let's begin!
First program!
One-on-one!
Heya.
Surprised you too, huh?
I just don't get it.
Is he my opponent?
I always hated school.
It's him... the one who
struggles with school stuff.
But it is what it is.
Just surrender the second
the battle starts, kid.
Got it?
I'm gonna win anyway.
That'll save me time and
you a world of pain.
My ability's just a little nasty, see.
I'd prefer to see it through, personally.
You've got some backbone, at least.
The first program will now begin.
Matches can only be resolved
through admission of defeat,
loss of consciousness, or death!
Please begin!
The cuffs are about to unlock.
Once they do, we can use our abilities.
Which means...
In five seconds, the battle begins.
Well, don't say I didn't warn you.
Let's go, freshman!
He turned the stick into a sword!
What the—
Sorry, kid! Can't fool me!
Just knock it off already!
You've got a nice bag of tricks,
but it's all over now.
I wonder why he won't use his ability.
It's not time yet.
What is that, a barricade?
Maybe you didn't get a
good fighting ability.
None of us knows what
happens when you lose.
So I get how you feel,
but just surrender already!
That's what I was waiting for.
You're messing with me.
It's over, kid.
You've run out of tricks.
Look, you got dragged into this, same as I did.
I don't wanna make mincemeat
out of you if I can help it.
That's not the reason I'm
not using my ability.
It's the opposite, actually.
Looks like it's showtime!
The opposite?
Yes.
I'm hesitant to use my ability
because it's so dangerous.
Hesitant because it's dangerous?
Quit bluffing, man.
I'm not bluffing.
I think you remember it.
Remember... what?
If you won't surrender,
I'll kill you before you can kill me!
The illusion...
My ability...
The "turn your hand into a cannon" ability!
Yes... I think you saw it, too.
The "turn your hand into
a cannon" ability...
That is a nasty ability.
This is how my...
So the sword reverts to a stick
when it leaves his hand?
I guess it's my turn now.
You've lost your weapon. You can't win.
Surrender.
I'll be forced to shoot you otherwise.
Well?
You little brat...
Fine.
I lose.
The winner, Akira Shiroyanagi!
Like I said, he's worth watching!
Yes... he was impressive.
Did you see?
He used his ability so well!
But why did he wait so long to use it?
He could have used that cannon at the start.
Did he manage to convince you
the cannon was his ability?
He created such an interesting illusion.
Akira said the cannon was his ability.
But it's not!
What? But I saw him use the cannon!
That was the illusion.
Akira made use...
of me.
<<Sophist>>
Mr. Akira Shiroyanagi
Your ability is
"whatever your opponent thinks your ability is."
Sophist. "Whatever your opponent
thinks your ability is."
He needs to arrange the right timing
to voice the ability to his opponent,
and create an environment
where they'll believe it.
"My ability is 'cannon.'"
He arranged the conditions
and timed it just right
to make sure his words were believed.
You're all that I hoped,
my sweet prince.
I made it through that one.
But there's a lot about this
ability I still need to test.
One's ability determines the
game's content and difficulty.
That's the part that makes
this ability interesting.
I'll start by doing as they wish,
playing through their
program using my ability.
Then I'll make that cat woman
regret ever giving it to me.
The game's just getting started.
<<Sophist>>
Mr. Akira Shiroyanagi
Your ability is
"whatever your opponent thinks your ability is."
Mion and Yang's
Next Episode Preview
Mion and Yang's Next Episode Preview!
Thanks so much for watching!
I'm Yang!
I'm Mion!
Did you enjoy our first episode of—
Ojamajo Mion!
N-No!
Of Battle Game in 5 Seconds!
Um, next episode is when our heroine's—
—training as Mion's magical
apprentice begins!
Will Mion's training break her?!
Please ignore that!
What kind of training is that, anyway?
Miss Mion, please stop
interrupting my preview—
We're running out of time! Hurry up, Yang!
We'll see you for episode 2!